

EDUCATION

National Forensic Sciences University July 2019 to Current M.Sc. Cyber Security 2021

Gujarat Technological University July 2014 to July 2018 B.e Computer Engineering 2018

SUMMARY

A Skilled Cyber Security Analyst with proficient and thorough expertise and a good understanding of information technology. Specialized in proactive monitoring of digital assets using SIEM (Splunk). Able to use various security tools to perform log analysis and to identify suspicious activity. Also, have working experience as a technical consultant so I can efficiently deal with people.

SKILLS

TOOLS: Metasploit, Nmap, Burpsuite, Autopsy, Maltego, Wireshark, Nessus, Shodan, Splunnk, Mobilyzer Forenisc Toolkit, FTK **TECHNOLOGY:** Vmware, Virtual box, Azure Cloud Computing, Google cloud Platform, Kali Linux, Windows, Ubuntu **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES:** Python, C programming, C++ Programming, Bash Scripting, HTML,CSS

EMPLOYMENT

COLGATE-PALMOLIVE

Cyber Security Intern Jan. 2021 to Current

Worked in SOC to help identify loopholes, malware, and any suspicious activities. Also worked on Threat-intel to provide a better security perspective.

REESS GMBH

Technical Consultant June 2018 to Dec. 2018

Provided deep insights to the technical knowledge base to the clients, working on client's requirements. Also was a part of a Research group to help create workshop contents.

PROJECTS

ACTIVE DIRECTORY PENTESTING

Jan. 2021 to Current

I worked on Active Directory pretesting, wherein I created an active directory with the domain controller and users and tried several ways an attacker can use to attack the domain.

DOCKER CONTAINER SECURITY

June 2020 to Dec. 2020

I Conducted Penetration Testing of the docker container by deploying it onto the local system and tried every possible way an attacker can use it to breach into containers.

JUICE JACKING Dec. 2019 to May 2020

Juice jacking was an attacker-based project, where-in an IoT device was used to grab data of victims from public places where charging stations are available.

ONLINE COMIC BOOKS 2016 to 2018

Online comic books is a PHP and ionic-based web app that allowed creators to create comic books online and share the same within the community.

VOLUNTEERING

MICROSOFT · Microsoft Student Partner

June 2017 to June 2018

Served as Microsoft Student Partner and Microsoft student Learn ambassador to promote new tools and technology to peers and colleges around Gujarat.

GIRLSCRIPT · Chapter Lead Ahmedabad

Apr. 2017 to Jan. 2018

I Served as a Chapter lead for GirlScript foundation (NGO promoting women in tech) for a period of 10+months. The primary role performed during this period included deliverables of tech talks and helping the core team for the India Summit held in Jan 2018.